Yanki Unger

Full Stack Developer 3+ years, Database Developer, Project Manager

Address: Jerusalem (flexible) Phone: 058-6009921 Date of Birth: 06/10/1994 E-mail: yanki044@gmail.com





Full Stack Developer at YKWeb, former Database Developer at BitWise MnM Inc & Front-end Developer. Organized, analytical, outside the box thinker, perfectionist, quick learner, a team member. Passionate yet professional. Learning and building with a DIY approach. Fluent in both English and Hebrew.

WORK EXPERIENCE:

2021 – 2022 Full Stack Developer – YKWeb – Remote, IL

JS, PHP, Laravel, MySQL, SendGrid, HTML, CSS

Responsible for developing new campaigns, as well as solving Real-time issues.

Worked with several US clients, including United Hatzalah.

2020 – 2021 Full Stack Developer – BitWise MnM Inc – Jerusalem, IL

Complex projects using Node.js, Angular 6, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, PHP,

Laravel, Regex, Python, API's, CSV, JSON, XML.

Supporting and programming for databases large and small using MySQL. Cloud

(Microsoft Azure, Amazon AWS).

2019 – 2020 Front-end Developer – Better Trader Ltd – *Jerusalem*

A HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery and other external libraries. Developed fully responsive pages for web, tablets and mobile.

EDUCATION:

2018 – 2019 Full Stack Developer, Webschool – Jerusalem, IL

Certificate with a 94/100 score.

HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, PHP, MYSQL, jQuery, REST / AJAX, REACT.JS, Node.JS, MongoDB.

2013 – 2014 A-Level Diplomas in Mathematics, Physics, Chemistry, Hasmonean – London, UK

SKILLS: • Agile • GitHub/GitLab • Project Manager • Designer • Xampp

LANGUAGES: • Hebrew (native) • English (native) • German (proficient)

CERTIFICATIONS: • Full Stack Developer – WebSchool, Jerusalem